ÁNGELA BLANCO MARÍN

ENGLISH TEACHER



Date of birth:

18/04/1994

CO N T A CT



Phone number:

660 141 330



Email Address:

angelablanco19@gmail.com



Address:

C/ Ladera de los Almendros 12B-4ºB - 28032 Madrid

A BO UT ME:

Six years of experience have allowed me to become a teacher who is not only extremely creative but also worried about having a wide range of teaching materials designed for children to enjoy classes as well as learning continuously.

In addition, being a federated athlete had provided me with valuable discipline as well as teamw ork skills.

LANGUAGES:

English - C1 Level (Advanced)
French - A1 Level (MCER)

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2012-2016 Degree in Bilingual Elementary Education – Antonio de Nebrija University (Madrid) and in South East Missouri University (SEMO), Cape Girardeau (MO – USA) (2014-2015)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sept 2021 – June 2022 COLEGIO GREDOS SAN DIEGO VALLECAS

- English, Science and Arts teacher for children from first grade
- Counselor of first grade

Sept 2020- June 2021 COLEGIO GREDOS SAN DIEGO MORATALAZ

- English, Science, Arts and Values classes for children from fourth, fifth and sixth grade.
- Counselor of sixth grade.

2017–2020 UK MADRID (Torrejón de Ardoz)

- English classes and workshops for pre-school children (hands-on activities, dancing, singing)
- Remedial classes given to children from 6 to 12-years-old in Biology in
- English
- English classes for children (all grades of elementary education and pre-school 1 and 2).
- English classes for adults (A1, A2, A2+) and speaking classes (Children,
- A2 and Bachillerato (B2).
- Pearson Examiner and invigilator.

2013-2017

- Private tutoring and remedial classes for six-year-old children (2016- 2017 School year).
- Voluntary work with people at risk of social exclusion, Cañada Real, Madrid.
- Spanish Private tutoring for kids from 6 to 8 years old in Cape Girardeau, Missouri.
- Internship as an English teacher at Colegio El Valle, Madrid, giving classes
- from second to sixth grade of primary of the following subjects: English, Biology, Socials and Arts.
- Learning centre after school with children from third to sixth grade.
- BULLE-BULLE, Centro Alternativo de Actividades y Juego Infantil (C/ Bulevar José Prat 29 – 28032 Madrid). Organisation, planning and monitoring of birthdays with children from 3 to 11 years old. Kitchen workshops and handicrafts.

EXTRA-ACADEMIC TRAINING

- Leisure time monitor: Academic training of 150 hours in Escuela Rastros (Madrid) and an internship of 120 hours in La Tallerteca with children from 3- to 8-year-olds doing different activities: games, workshops, gymkhanas, dances, songs and the activity assessment.
- Coeducation and gender perspective course (June 2019)
- Food handler certificate (June 2019)
- **JC Madrid Deporte y Cultura**. Leisure time monitor planning environment and recycling activities with children from 3 to 12 years old. (July 2019.July and August 2020, July 2021)
- Two webinars by Pearson: "Gamify our English classroom" (January 2020) and
- "Getting practical: great ideas for class" (March 2020)
- C1.2 course in UKMADRID 2019-2020
- TEFL Course May 2022